[
    {
        "question": "Who are the most important people in your life?", 
        "answer": "family and friends"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is ‘home’?", 
        "answer": "Miami" 
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is ‘home’?", 
        "answer": "Miami"   
    },
    {
        "question": "What’s your big passion?", 
        "answer":"saving the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you read reviews, or just go with your gut?", 
        "answer":"gut feeling" 
    },
    {
        "question": "What’s the best meal you’ve ever had?", 
        "answer":"seafood in italy"  
    },
    {
        "question": "What are your hobbies, and how did you get into them?", 
        "answer": "sports and reading"
    },
    {
        "question": "Would you say you’re more of an extrovert or an introvert?", 
        "answer":"extrovert or introvert"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you had a free plane ticket, where would you like to go?", 
        "answer":"anywhere and everywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of music are you into?", 
        "answer":"all music" 
    },
    {
        "question": "What toppings are needed to create the perfect burger?", 
        "answer":"onions, cheese, mustard, pickles, lettuce" 
    }
    
]